var questionLib = [{
    question: "Javascript is _________ language.",
    answers: ["None of These",
        "Application",
        "Scripting",
        "Programming"],
    cAnswer: 3
},
{
    question: "JavaScript is ______ Side Scripting Language.",
    answers: ["None of These",
        "ISP",
        "Browser",
        "Server"],
    cAnswer: 3
},

{
    question: "JavaScript is designed for following purpose",
    answers: ["To add interactivity to HTML Pages.",
        "To Execute Query Related to DB on Server",
        "To Style HTML Pages",
        "To Perform Server Side Scripting Opertion"],
    cAnswer: 1
},
{
    question: "Select Appropriate Option(s) :  JavaScript is can be written",
    answers: ["None of these",
        "directly on the Server Script",
        "directly into HTML pages",
        "directly into JS file and included into HTML"],
    cAnswer: 2
},
{
    question: "JavaScript Code is written inside file having extension __________.",
    answers: [".jvs",
        ".js",
        ".javascript",
        ".jsc"],
    cAnswer: 2
},
{
    question: "Why JavaScript is called as Lightweight Programming Language ?",
    answers: ["because we can add programming functionality inside JS",
        "because JS is available free of cost.",
        "because JS is client side scripting",
        "because JS can provide programming functionality inside but up to certain extend."],
    cAnswer: 4
},
{
    question: "Local Browser used for validations on the Web Pages uses __________.",
    answers: ["HTML",
        "JS",
        "Java",
        "CSS"],
    cAnswer: 2
},
{
    question: "Select all the correct option(s). State the correct place of JS Code inside HTML",
    answers: ["All of these",
        "Inside Single JavaScript File",
        "Inside Body",
        "Inside Head"],
    cAnswer: 1
},
{
    question: "Which of the following Attribute is used to include External JS code inside your HTML Document -",
    answers: ["ext",
        "scrip",
        "src",
        "Link"],
    cAnswer: 3
},
{
    question: "Which attribute is used to specifies that the script is executed when the page has finished parsing (only for external scripts)",
    answers: ["defer",
        "type",
        "async",
        "parse"],
    cAnswer: 1
}

]

